FIORELLA ÁLVAREZ JIMÉNEZ

Email: fiorellaaj@hotmail.com.

Skype: Fiorella.alvarez5 cellphone: 3002360068 City: Barranquilla, Colombia.



PROFILE

Master of Teaching with LKT: Managing Talent, Learning and Innovation in Organisations, Bachelor Degree in Business Administration. Work experience in logistic and port business, with the following skills: Team work and leadership, proactive and responsible, crisis management, communicative skills, elaboration and certification of sustainability reports by the GRI (Global Reporting Initiative) and knowledge in Neuro-linguistic programming (NLP).

Computer skills: Management of Microsoft Office, SAP, Prezzi, Symbaloo and ONBASE.

Languages: Spanish (native), English (fluent), Italian (fluent), French (basic).

EDUCATION

- Master's Degree in Teaching with LKT: Managing Talent, Learning and Innovation in Organisations.
 Universidad Autónoma de Barcelona. Barcelona, España. (2017)
- Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration. Universidad del Norte. Barranquilla, Colombia. (2013)

EXPERIENCE

General Coordinator. Fundación Puerto de Barranquilla. Barranquilla, Colombia. (october 2016-august 2017).

Principal Functions: Legal representation of the Foundation, coordinate the strategic administrative and operational planning, supervision and promotion of the work team, periodical presentation of the special management report to the Board of Directors and Assembly, create strategic alliances for the sustainability of the Foundation and relationship with the Foundation's stakeholders.

Chief Executive Assistant. Puerto de Barranquilla. Barranquilla, Colombia. (january 2015-october 2016).

Principal Functions: Follow-up of the projects of the Presidency Committee, accompaniment in external advisory projects, planning of national and international events, budgetary analysis of the Presidency, and general documentary assistance.

• Financial and Customer Service Coordinator. Laboratorio Orthodontic Merdent. Barranquilla, Colombia. (march 2014-january 2015).

Principal Functions: Claims management, management of post sales communications and customer loyalty, analysis of customer service indicators, preparation of the balance sheet, income statement and cash flow, preparation of the statements of accounts, analysis of the past due portfolio, collection of the past due portfolio, payment programming.

HSEQ Coordinator. Zona Franca de Barranquilla S.A. U.O.Z.F. Barranquilla, Colombia. (january-june de 2013).

Principal Functions: Coordinate the preparation of the annual Sustainability Report under the Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) standards, support in the process of certification of quality standards ISO 14001 and OHSAS 18001, and analysis of the status of the compliance and civil liability policies of the organization.

 Project Manager Assistant. Zona Franca de Barranquilla S.A. U.O.Z.F. Barranquilla, Colombia. (february-december de 2012).

Principal Functions: General assistance to the Project Management, and analysis of the compliance and civil liability policies of the organization.